crowdox.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy - CrowdOx

Privacy is important to us at CrowdOx. Please review this Privacy Policy for a description of our privacy practices, an explanation of how we may use any personal information we collect on this website, and ways to opt out. Please refer to our Terms of Service for any additional information, including but not limited to defined terms. 

### General

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online from Users (as that term is defined in our Terms of Service) of this website (the " **Site** "). In this policy, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to your personal information. 

### Personal Information

We collect information about our Users in three ways: (a) directly from the User, (b) from our Site web server logs, and (c) through cookies. We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you and to associated User generated content with the correct originator of that content. We don't share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

In addition, when you engage in certain Services (as that term is defined in our Terms of Service), CrowdOx may collect your credit/debit card information. This information is secured using industry-standard encryption technology. CrowdOx will use this information solely to complete your order and will not share this information with outside parties, except to the extent necessary to complete the order or comply with applicable law. 

### User-Supplied Content & Information

Users are encouraged to post comments, feedback, and testimonials. Please do not submit any confidential, proprietary or sensitive personally identifiable information (e.g. Social Security Number; driver's license number; or credit card, bank account or other financial information) (collectively, "Sensitive Information"). If you submit any Sensitive Information, you do so at your own risk and we will not be liable to you or responsible for consequences of your submission. 

User-supplied content and information that you provide to us when posting text, comments, or other information may be used to provide information to one or more third parties for market research or marketing purposes in accordance with the law. CrowdOx is the sole owner of all information obtained at this Site. 

### Web Server Logs

When you visit our Site, we may track information about your visit and store that information in our Site web server logs, which are records of the activities on our sites. The servers automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the information we may collect include but are not limited to: 

  * your unique Internet protocol (IP) address;
  * the name of your unique Internet service provider;
  * the town/city, county/state and country from which you access our Site;
  * the kind of browser or computer you use;
  * the number of links you click within the Site;
  * the date and time of your visit;
  * the web page from which you arrived to our Site;
  * the pages you viewed on the Site; and
  * certain searches/queries that you conducted via our Site(s).

The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the Site, analyze its usage, identify information or services that are most relevant to a particular User, protect the Site and its content from inappropriate use, and improve the User's experience.

### Cookies

In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, our websites and applications may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites during your visits. Cookies allow us to save preferences for you so you won't have to re-enter them each time you visit. 

The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you don't accept cookies. 

### Protection of Personal Information

We take certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat or circumvent our security measures. This Site may contain links to websites operated by other people, companies or entities that are not controlled by us. We have no responsibility or liability for the policies, activities or content of these other sites. By using this Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Access to Information

We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other User data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows:

  * to agents, third parties, Site vendors and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us;
  * if we are unable to assist with your matter, but know an unaffiliated company that may be able to help you, we may refer you and share information you provided us with that party; and
  * as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another company or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.

### Correcting, Amending, or Deleting Personal Information and/or Opt-Out of Future Communications

[Contact us](mailto:he%6Cl%6F@cro%77dox.com) to:

  * see what data we have about you, if any;
  * change/correct any data we have about you;
  * ask us to delete any data we have about you; and/or
  * opt out of future communications from us.

### Additional Questions or Concerns

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:he%6Cl%6F@cro%77dox.com). If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post the policy changes here.
